Contact

+65 98803807 (Mobile) woochunonn90@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/chunonn-woo (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Digital Business
Design Thinking
Employee Value Proposition

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Chinese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Audit and Due Diligence: Priorities and Best Practices

Think Like a Lawyer to Make Decisions and Solve Problems

Excel for Banking Professionals

Honors-Awards

RP Athlete Development Grant (Taekwondo)

Certificate of Merit

Chun Onn Woo

Strategic Business Planning - Treasures at DBS Bank Singapore Singapore

Summary

As a skilled and experienced associate in the banking industry, I have a demonstrated track record of success in troubleshooting, investigation, and leadership. In addition to being a proactive team player and excellent troubleshooter, I am also highly tech-savvy and able to quickly adapt to new concepts and technologies. I am confident in my ability to contribute value to any team and organization.

Experience

DBS Bank

3 years 3 months

Strategic Business Planning - DBS Treasures January 2024 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Employee Value Proposition. Business Process and Governance.

Business Development Manager - DBS Treasures Offshore December 2021 - January 2024 (2 years 2 months) Singapore

Specializing in offshore account opening and customer KYC, I ensure smooth and compliant onboarding of new clients. I collaborate with functional teams to streamline processes and stay up-to-date on industry changes, and track and monitor business acquisitions to ensure compliance. My efforts have improved the efficiency and accuracy of our account opening processes, resulting in higher customer satisfaction.

Standard Chartered Bank

3 years 5 months

Relationship Service Manager - International Priority Banking September 2019 - December 2021 (2 years 4 months) Singapore

Relationship Service Manager in International Banking Priority Clients - Business Development Team

Branch Sales & Service Manager August 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 2 months) Singapore

As a personal banker for the mass market segment, I adeptly resolved a wide range of banking issues for walk-in clients, enhancing their customer experience through my problem-solving skills and service excellence.

OCBC Bank

Polytechnic Trainee Bank Officer - Bank Teller January 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 8 months) Singapore

Began my career in the banking industry in January 2017 as a bank teller through the Polytechnic Trainee Bank Officer Program. This program provided me with valuable training and experience, and I was able to apply my skills and knowledge in my role as a bank teller, where I was responsible for providing high standards of customer service and handling a range of financial transactions.

Education

University College Dublin

Bachelor of Business Studies (Hons), Digital Business · (April 2021 - January 2023)

Republic Polytechnic

Diploma, Materials Science · (2011 - 2014)